{
    "subject": "resource/Esther_Rolle",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "Actress",
    "human_readable": "Esther Rolle's occupation is Actress.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8984398245811462,
            "question": "What made Esther Rolle a notable actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8456872701644897,
            "question": "What was Esther Rolle's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.771561861038208,
            "question": "Did Esther Rolle have a successful acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7089467644691467,
            "question": "Was Esther Rolle known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5700032711029053,
            "question": "What kind of roles did Esther Rolle likely play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4968452453613281,
            "question": "What contributed to Esther Rolle's popularity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4218805134296417,
            "question": "What is Esther Rolle best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3853570520877838,
            "question": "Why is Esther Rolle remembered in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3662601709365845,
            "question": "In what field did Esther Rolle work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3416972756385803,
            "question": "Can you name any famous movies or shows featuring Esther Rolle?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Esther Rolle's occupation is Actress.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5323_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what field did Esther Rolle work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5323_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is Esther Rolle remembered in the entertainment industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5323_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Esther Rolle best known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5323_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5323_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5323_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5323_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5323_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5323_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5323_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5323_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5323_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5323_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5323_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents provided confirm that Esther Rolle was an American actress, and one of her notable roles was as Florida Evans on the CBS television sitcom Maude. There is no indication or mention of any other occupation besides acting."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Esther Elizabeth Rolle was an actress, which supports the triple stating her occupation as Actress."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}